24article.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Statement | כללי מערכת- free Article directory

### Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the ArticleDeck treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit an article, or request an article via email. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the ArticleDeck web site, nor does it extend to people that ArticleDeck does not employ or manage.

### Author Anonymity

ArticleDeck does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Authors who wish to remain anonymous should either **NOT** complete the Author Profile in their member accounts **OR** complete it using a Pen Name.

Although discovering an Author's real identity is difficult if a Pen Name is used in submitting articles, there are several ways for that information to be found if the Author Profile is completed with your real name and identity details.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

ArticleDeck maintains your email address and other pertinent information in a secure database. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. ArticleDeck, however, reserves the right to contact ArticleDeck members via email as deemed necessary. Such mailings will always include detailed unsubscribe information, providing members the option of removing themselves from future ArticleDeck mailings at any time.

### Security

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to ArticleDeck staff.

### Information Collection

ArticleDeck collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.

### Information Use

If you are ArticleDeck Author member, your use of our service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your article(s). In exchange, ArticleDeck reserves the right to use the contact information collected during member registration to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide a free newsletter, to inform you of additions to ArticleDeck, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact us.

Spam complaints will result in membership termination.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

ArticleDeck may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

Author Articles

More From This Author

Amitech USA, Ltd. is a member of one the world's leading pipe technology and manufacturing companies.  The Amiantit Group is an international organization with a track record of growth-orientated...

After the Attorney General of Massachusetts promulgated comprehensive regulations governing the advertising and sale of cigarettes, smokeless tobacco, and cigars, petitioners, a group of tobacco...

Petitioner sought to fill wetlands for beach front subdivision, which Rhode Island Coastal Resources Management Council rejected, ruling that the proposal did not satisfy the standards for...

Petitioner was ordered deported for his criminal record. No country would accept him and Cambodia did not have a repatriation treaty. He challenged his detention indefinitely as...

The Mushroom Promotion, Research, and Consumer Information Act mandates that fresh mushroom handlers pay assessments used primarily to fund advertisements promoting mushroom sales. Respondent...

Related Articles

Related Articles

When everyone just talks about the biggest fashion brands even in the domain of sunglasses, they forget that there are other brands that only focus on these accessories and nothing else. Dragon is...

The aluminium privacy screens represent quite a modern and attractive design that will definitely add value to any property. They are suitable to presentation walls, gate features, privacy screening,...

If you live in a place where your neighbors can observe your activities inside the house, then you really need to do something about it because I’m sure you want privacy. One great manner to get...

There are many reasons why you may want to erase your browser history because no matter how little or how much you use your computer and internet you leave a trace behind. If you think you are not...

Blinds Warrington are the perfect way to offer shade and privacy to your home. You will be able to control the amount of light coming through the window by adjusting the blinds. There are various...

Latest Articles

Latest Articles

Thinking about running a faa drug testing program as soon as possible? Then, it would be a good moment to learn more on what you have to do and what is best to avoid. From preparing the workplace to...

When you spent an important part of your finances on new appliances you want them to last for as long as possible. However, after daily use, any type of appliance will start to have issues and you...

There is a very delicate relationship between an application and how you put it to use. When it comes to sound, you look for the best experience with minimum hassle. Thanks to the advancements in...

Thinking how is best to manage a drug testing program? Worried that the program won’t be implemented according to the highest standards? In this case, there is nothing else to do but look for a...

Worried about the next faa drug testing program you have to run in the company? Not sure how to best manage these procedures? Well, in this situation, the only thing to do is to contact a company...

Most Read Articles

Most Read Articles

Creative issues always arise when businessmen visit banner printers for Banners and Signs New York. It is not uncommon for creative designers and business owners to come at loggerheads over...

Hot, spicy and sizzling wallpapers of south Indian actresses have the potential to attract many an eyeball. Even when you are forced to work by your tight schedules and meetings just a glance through...

Mothers Day Poems Mother when you're not I regaré with my tears oh mother! the garden the House and the yard malvones; It will be when your absence palpiten Geraniums and cry the gardenias and...

Accidents at execute atmosphere are an work-related danger and sometimes expected. You can only wish they do not occur to you and take highest possible care that they don't; but you cannot wish them...
